<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kansas City Real Estate</title>
    <description>Our mission at SDG and Associates is to be your best resource for Kansas City real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The SDG and Associates, your professional Kansas City Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 12:24:12 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 12:24:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Conversation with Mortgage Professionals</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BGVi7hIAyXo?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our guests are two highly respected Mortgage Professionals with Fairway Mortgage that will answer questions about what has happened these past 2 weeks and the implications for you and your family!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 17:49:10 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-conversation-with-mortgage-professionals.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-conversation-with-mortgage-professionals.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Do's and Don'ts of Travelling in 2020</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4Lj4oolFV44?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s featured guest is Tracy Gervais, a local travel agent. Join us as we discuss the DOs and DON’Ts of travel in 2020!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 16:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-dos-and-donts-of-travelling-in-2020.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-dos-and-donts-of-travelling-in-2020.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Conversation with Amber and Frank, CPAs</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/7PKsVxhdShc?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Catch up with Shannon from her conversation with Amber Goerging and Frank Granatino from Goerging &amp;amp; Granatino Public Accounting Firm by watching the recorded Zoom video above!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out their COVID-19 resources on their website: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ggkccpa.com/category/covid-19/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.ggkccpa.com/category/covid-19/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 13:11:38 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/conversation-with-amber-and-frank-cpas.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/conversation-with-amber-and-frank-cpas.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Quick Introduction to Our Team and How We Can Help You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Xy4QUtkST_8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;center&gt;We had an amazing year in 2019, and with our new video blog, we&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to an even better one in 2020. Here&amp;rsquo;s what you can expect in the coming months.&lt;/center&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re here to introduce ourselves, brag about our team, and celebrate our successes in 2019. &lt;strong&gt;Our names are Shannon Doser and Cami Savage and we’re with SDG and Associates and Keller Williams Realty Partners.&lt;/strong&gt; We have been in real estate in Kansas City for a combined 26 years and in business together for the last three-and-a-half years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve worked with many of you one-on-one, and many of you have had the pleasure of working with one of our six talented associates: Michele Harlow, Karen Hill, Chandra Ward, Stephanie Vielhauer, Andy Olson, or Court Hendrickson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Thanks to all of you, we had an amazing year in 2019.%20http://localhost:4000/a-quick-introduction-to-our-team-and-how-we-can-help-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Thanks to all of you, we had an amazing year in 2019.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to thank all of you for an amazing 2019. Together, we helped 90 families buy and sell their homes across the KC Metro. With nearly $28 million in closed volume, &lt;strong&gt;we’re proud to say that 95% of our business came from referrals, past clients, our trusted vendor partners, and the relationships we have with agents around the country.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we look forward to 2020, we are encouraged that national home equity is forecasted to rise between 2.5% and 3.5%, which is great news for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Throughout this year, you’ll be hearing from all of us as we share valuable info about the housing market,&lt;/strong&gt; helpful tips for taking care of your own home, and special events that we’re hosting in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for us in the meantime or any real estate needs that we can assist with, feel free to reach out to us via phone or email. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 11:13:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/a-quick-introduction-to-our-team-and-how-we-can-help-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-quick-introduction-to-our-team-and-how-we-can-help-you.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To Our Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Our market remains busy, and it’s still an opportune time to command a high price selling your home.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We know what’s happening in the KC Metro area, specifically pertaining to home values, that will directly affect you.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we’ll be posting two monthly video messages on this blog to keep you updated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will be valuable and useful in helping you stay on top of what’s happening in the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check back because content will be coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to keep you updated on what’s happening in the KC Metro area!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
