<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kansas City Real Estate</title>
    <description>Our mission at SDG and Associates is to be your best resource for Kansas City real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The SDG and Associates, your professional Kansas City Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 14:07:18 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 14:07:18 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED! Well-Maintained Condo Near Westport, The Plaza and KU Med!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/YoyU2Yri9kY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4213-clark-ave-1-kansas-city-mo-64111&quot;&gt;4213 Clark Ave #1, Kansas City, MO  64111&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med&quot;&gt;Well-Maintained Condo Near Westport, The Plaza and KU Med!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://4213clark.sdgandassociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4213 Clark Avenue Unit #1&lt;/a&gt;, a well-maintained and super functional two bedroom, one full bath condo near Westport, The Plaza and KU Med. Enjoy easy access to downtown and convenient walking distance to entertainment and shopping..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://4213clark.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4213Clark.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG34” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter the home and notice the easy flow between the light and bright living spaces. The living room offers crown moulding and a beautiful wood sliding glass door leading to your private patio. The living room is open to the cheery fully equipped kitchen highlighting large ceramic tile flooring, an abundance of cabinetry and counter space, full tile backsplash with mosaic accents, and an island with bar seating illuminated by pendant lighting. Stainless steel appliances include the refrigerator, smooth surface range, built-in microwave, dishwasher and disposal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both bedrooms feature refreshing lighted ceiling fans and generous sized closets, while the full bath offers a granite vanity and a shower over tub with lovely tile surround. There is also a stackable washer and dryer that stays with the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will enjoy being steps away from the private pool and will appreciate the gated parking spot right next to the unit. The community also includes building maintenance, lawn maintenance, and trash pick up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG34” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED! DARLING HOME with Fantastic Indoor and Outdoor Space!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WqyFSHoHhHk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4141-holly-street-kansas-city-mo-64111&quot;&gt;4141 Holly Street, Kansas City, MO  64111&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;darling-home-with-fantastic-indoor-and-outdoor-space&quot;&gt;DARLING HOME with Fantastic Indoor and Outdoor Space!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://4141Holly.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4141 Holly Street&lt;/a&gt;, a DARLING Circa 1909 home offering three bedrooms, two full baths, and 1,544 square feet of living space with fantastic gathering spaces, both inside and out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://4141Holly.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4141Holly.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG33” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A grassy front yard with mature shade trees invites you to the expansive covered front porch spanning the length of the home. What a wonderful spot to enjoy a cool glass of lemonade while chatting with a friend on a lovely summer day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter through the front door with sidelights and into the foyer. Take note of the enchanting window to your left with inlaid glass, the rich hardwood floors found throughout the home, extensive wood trim elements, and soothing color palette cheerfully welcoming you in. The first floor flows easily for comfortable living and entertaining, and the living room showcases a charming decorative corner fireplace, refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and windows overlooking both the front and side yards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hardwood floors continue through an archway into the formal dining room highlighting crown moulding, a lighted ceiling fan, and an enchanting bay window with cushioned seat offering extra seating or a space to relax in the southern exposure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to the dining room is the spacious kitchen showcasing abundant cabinetry and counter space, full mosaic tile backsplash, French door refrigerator, smooth surface range, built-in microwave, and large ceramic tile flooring. You’ll also love the cute coffee bar station!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the kitchen, 15-lite garden doors open to the light-filled sunroom with walls of windows, a lighted ceiling fan, laundry area, and a door leading to the deck. Currently, the owners are using this space as a spare bedroom with a fold-out couch, and this room would also make for a sunny first floor home office. Also on the main level is the converted full bathroom with new shower, perfect for overnight guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascend the stairs to the upper level with unique bedroom layouts. The master bedroom features hardwood floors, recessed lighting, ceiling fan, make-up station or office nook, and even has room for exercise equipment. The full bath offers decorative wainscoting, and a shower over tub with tile surround. There are also two secondary bedrooms on the upper level, also with wood floors and ceiling fans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, gather with family and friends on the newer 12x12 raised deck providing wonderful views of the grassy and fenced backyard with mature shade tree. Take the stairs to the yard below where adults, kids and pets alike will enjoy recreating in this beautiful space. You will also appreciate the included storage shed, double gate entry to the backyard, off-street parking, and the central heating and air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG33” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-darling-home-with-fantastic-indoor-and-outdoor-space.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-darling-home-with-fantastic-indoor-and-outdoor-space.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-darling-home-with-fantastic-indoor-and-outdoor-space.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED  ~ Own on Belinder Road and Enjoy Views of Mission Hills Golf Course!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/PtVvNCZmbPg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5332-belinder-road-fairway-ks-66205&quot;&gt;5332 Belinder Road, Fairway, KS  66205&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;own-on-belinder-road-and-enjoy-views-of-mission-hills-golf-course&quot;&gt;Own on Belinder Road and Enjoy Views of Mission Hills Golf Course!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is your chance to own on Belinder Road and enjoy the views of Mission Hills Golf Course! Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://5332Belinder.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;5332 Belinder Road&lt;/a&gt; in Fairway, a darling two bedroom, one full bath ranch home offering 1,437 square feet of living space with location within the coveted, award winning Shawnee Mission East School District. This home also has access to an attic offering the possibility of expansion and the chance to create your own second floor master suite retreat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://5332Belinder.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;5332Belinder.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG32” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be welcomed home by a grassy front yard and long driveway leading to the covered front porch. Upon entry, notice the gorgeous hardwood floors, today’s color palette, crown moulding and trim elements, and abundant windows creating light and bright living areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The living room features a cozy gas start wood burning fireplace with tile surround and embellished wood mantel, and is open to the dining room showcasing a wall of windows overlooking the front yard with lovely views. Additional highlights include attractive chair railing and chandelier lighting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through French doors is the bright and cheery sun room with large tile flooring, built-in cabinet and counter space, a huge window overlooking the backyard, and a door opening to the patio. This is a great space for creating a home office, reading nook, or coffee break room if you are working from home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the dining room, living room, and sunroom you have access to the enchanting fully-equipped kitchen, making entertaining a breeze. The kitchen showcases abundant white cabinetry, great counter space, hardwood floors, full tile backsplash, and pantry. All white appliances include the refrigerator, gas range, built-in microwave, and dishwasher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a true ranch home, both bedrooms are on the main level and feature hardwood flooring, double wide closets, and crown moulding, while the master also has a refreshing lighted ceiling fan. The endearing full bath has a pedestal sink, attractive beadboard, and a shower over tub with tile surround.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, enjoy spending time with family and friends on the patio with privacy screen providing beautiful views of the expansive, grassy and fenced yard with majestic shade tree. This is a wonderful yard for your furry friends or creating your own at-home getaway, plus there is even room for a garden with southern exposure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional features include an attached garage, double wide driveway for extra off-street parking, central heating and air, and the washer and dryer are included as well. What are you waiting for? Now is your chance to live in a highly desirable neighborhood and begin creating cherished memories today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-own-on-belinder-road-and-enjoy-views-of-mission-hills-golf-course.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-own-on-belinder-road-and-enjoy-views-of-mission-hills-golf-course.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-own-on-belinder-road-and-enjoy-views-of-mission-hills-golf-course.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED and 1st OPEN HOUSE 5/26, 4-6pm</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vtXo06xpc6Q?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;9429-greenway-lane-lenexa-ks-66215&quot;&gt;9429 Greenway Lane, Lenexa, KS  66215&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;picture-perfect-in-lenexa-beautifully-maintained-and-updated&quot;&gt;Picture Perfect in Lenexa! Beautifully Maintained and Updated!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GOING LIVE AT MIDNIGHT and we will be hosting the first &lt;strong&gt;OPEN HOUSE&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;strong&gt;Wednesday, May 26th from 4 - 6pm!&lt;/strong&gt; We look forward to seeing you and showing you your next home…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/greenway-oh-jl-unbranded.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;1080&quot; height=&quot;1080&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://9429Greenway.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;9429 Greenway Lane&lt;/a&gt;, a picture perfect home on a cul-de-sac corner lot offering three bedrooms plus a non-conforming fourth, two full and one half baths, and 2,165 square feet of beautifully maintained and updated living space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://9429Greenway.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;9429Greenway.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG27” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the many highlights include a 1 YEAR YOUNG roof and 5” aluminum gutters, newer water heater, beautiful wood floors, vaulted ceilings, family rec room, screened porch, deck and a fenced yard. Plus, this home is located in the Award Winning Shawnee Mission School District!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you approach the home, be greeted by a grassy front yard, mature shade trees, and stone exterior accents. Enter into the light and bright great room with soaring cathedral ceiling, skylight, stunning wood floors, refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and a lovely floor-to-ceiling window framed by built-ins on each side, perfect for displaying your treasures. Gather by the handsome masonry gas log fireplace or entertain guests by way of the patio door opening to the screened porch. The great room is open to the dining room, which features the lovely hardwood floors, chandelier lighting and another large window.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to the dining room is the charming eat-in kitchen showcasing abundant white cabinetry with under cabinet lighting and display cabinets, the gorgeous wood floors, generous counter space, an undermount double sink illuminated by chic pendant lighting, and a basket-weave marble tile backsplash. Stainless steel appliances include the smooth surface range, built-in microwave, dishwasher and disposal. The breakfast area offers a lighted ceiling fan and bay window providing views through the screened porch to the back yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will appreciate that all three bedrooms are on the main level, and the stunning master suite showcases a high vaulted ceiling with refreshing lighted fan, closet organizing system, and private full bath with expansive vanity and separate water closet with large walk-in tiled shower. The second bedroom features beautiful wood flooring and closet system, while the third bedroom highlights a ceiling fan and closet system. The second full bath includes a shower over tub and skylight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs, the finished basement features a huge family rec room with expansive wet bar &amp;amp; built-in storage. The bonus room includes a closet and would make for a great non-conforming 4th bedroom, in-home gym, office or study. There is also a convenient half bath on this level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beautiful outdoor living areas are great spaces for everyday living or hosting your friends and family. The large screened porch with huge vaulted ceiling provides year-round enjoyment with a door leading to the expansive deck with pergola. Both of these areas provide serene views of the perfectly manicured and landscaped backyard. Adults, kids and pets alike will love enjoying these beautiful spaces. Additional home features include an attached 2-car garage with automatic openers and keyless entry, central heating and air, storm doors, and a humidifier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start creating lasting memories in this picture perfect home today! For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-and-1st-open-house-526-4-6pm.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-and-1st-open-house-526-4-6pm.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-and-1st-open-house-526-4-6pm.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Open House</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ Delightful True Ranch Home in Shawnee with Oversized Back Yard!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/H9iKh1yqhNY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;11410-w-67th-terrace-shawnee-ks-66203&quot;&gt;11410 W. 67th Terrace, Shawnee, KS  66203&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;delightful-true-ranch-home-in-shawnee-with-oversized-back-yard&quot;&gt;Delightful True Ranch Home in Shawnee with Oversized Back Yard!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://67th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;11410 W 67th Terrace&lt;/a&gt;, a delightful True Ranch home in Shawnee with an oversized back yard and so many updates! Enjoy a new roof, kitchen with new granite counters, backsplash, stainless steel dishwasher, stove and hood, newer heater, newer carpet, and the heater in the garage stays. If that’s not enough, this home is located in the award winning Shawnee Mission School District!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://67th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;67th.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG28” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delightful curb appeal, a grassy front yard, cheerful exterior, and covered front porch with curved steps and stylish columns all welcome you home. Enter to the living room with beautiful hardwood flooring, a soothing color palette, crown moulding, a refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and a large window inviting natural light to fill the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continue to the eat-in kitchen highlighting abundant white cabinetry, plenty of new, gorgeous granite counters with undermount sink, stainless steel appliances, subway tile backsplash, pantry, and newer smooth surface range, vent hood, and dishwasher. The delightful dining area has crown moulding, lighted ceiling fan, and a door opening to the rear deck and yard. The easy flow between the living spaces is perfect for daily living and entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a true ranch home, both bedrooms are on the main level and feature newer carpet, lighted ceiling fans, and crown moulding. The updated full hall bath offers tile flooring and a shower over tub with stunning, modern tile surround.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, entertain family and friends on the deck overlooking the oversized, grassy and fenced backyard. What a wonderful spot to enjoy an evening barbecue, a game of volleyball, a round of croquet, or for the kids and pets to frolic and play. There are also two spacious sheds offering additional storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional home features include an attached garage with heater, extra parking pad, central heating and air, storm windows, and location close to schools, parks and shopping. This darling, true ranch home is waiting for you to begin calling home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG28” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-delightful-true-ranch-home-in-shawnee-with-oversized-back-yard.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 16:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-delightful-true-ranch-home-in-shawnee-with-oversized-back-yard.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-delightful-true-ranch-home-in-shawnee-with-oversized-back-yard.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ This Home is a True Gem! Don't Miss It!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/waxN0LJkL8s?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;6122-w-76th-place-prairie-village-ks-66208&quot;&gt;6122 W. 76th Place, Prairie Village KS  66208&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;this-home-is-a-true-gem-dont-miss-it&quot;&gt;This Home is a True Gem! Don’t Miss It!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://76th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;6122 W. 76th Place&lt;/a&gt; in the Prairie Fields community of Prairie Village. This charming home offers 3 bedrooms, 2.1 baths, and 1,752 square feet of living space with so much to fall in love with, including a NEW roof, NEW furnace, and NEWER A/C, water heater, gutter covers, and sump pump, and the sewer line was replaced in 2017. If that’s not enough, this home is located in the award winning Shawnee Mission East School District! So much has been taken care of during the ownership of this home, and yet there are still opportunities for the next owner to make it uniquely their own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://76th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;76th.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour an current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG4” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be greeted by a grassy front yard with mature shade tree and meander down the path to the welcoming front door. Step inside and notice the gorgeous wood floors, inviting colors, and the light and bright living spaces. The living room also features a wood burning masonry fireplace with embellished mantel surround, and a large window overlooking the front yard allowing natural light to illuminate the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to the living room is the beautiful formal dining room showcasing a wall of crisp white built-in cabinets and shelving to display your treasures, hardwood floors, and a wall of windows providing serene views of the deck and backyard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dining room opens to the extremely functional and spacious eat-in kitchen highlighting abundant solid wood cabinetry, great counter space, tile backsplash, built-in desk, pantry and island with additional storage. Appliances include the refrigerator, range, dishwasher, microwave and disposal. The cheery breakfast area, currently being used as a sitting room, features large windows with views of the backyard and a door opening to the deck. The easy flow between these spaces makes entertaining a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main level master suite highlights wood floors, a refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and lock-off access to the en-suite full bath. There is also a connected half bath creating an efficient separate solution for the main level second and third bedrooms – very creative!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs, the finished basement offers a family room, bonus room that could be used as a home office or non-conforming 4th bedroom, and the second bath with separate shower. There is also unfinished space for your storage needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, spend time on the recently refinished low-profile deck providing views of the lush yard. With beautiful landscaping, this fully fenced level backyard is perfect for get togethers with family and friends, kids that like to run, your furry friends, or your inner gardener.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional features include an attached garage with opener, keyless entry, and new pulleys installed, newer in-ground sprinkler system, central heating and air, humidifier, thermal windows, and did we mention — location in the Shawnee Mission East School District! Welcome home!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG4” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-this-home-is-a-true-gem-dont-miss-it.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 18:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-this-home-is-a-true-gem-dont-miss-it.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-this-home-is-a-true-gem-dont-miss-it.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED TODAY! Super Cute and MOVE-IN READY Ranch Home!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OLvm23FEbsE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5249-outlook-street-mission-ks-66202&quot;&gt;5249 Outlook Street, Mission KS 66202&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;super-cute-and-move-in-ready-ranch-home&quot;&gt;Super Cute and MOVE-IN READY Ranch Home!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This beautiful home was &lt;strong&gt;JUST LISTED TODAY!&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://outlook.sdgandassociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;5249 Outlook Street&lt;/a&gt; in the Wiedenmann Ridge community of Mission, a super cute, MOVE-IN READY two bedroom ranch home on a corner lot. Some of the highlights include hardwood floors, a floor-to ceiling fireplace, patio, fenced yard, attached garage, central air, and location within the award winning Shawnee Mission School District. You will also appreciate the quick and easy access to the highway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://outlook.ihousenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Outlook.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG2” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delightful curb appeal greets you as you approach the home. The grassy front yard with mature shade tree welcomes you to the pathway leading to the front porch. Step inside and notice the gleaming hardwood floors and all the windows creating light and bright living areas. The living room features a refreshing lighted ceiling fan, large windows overlooking the front and side yards, and a handsome floor-to-ceiling corner fireplace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hardwood floors continue to the dining room with stylish drum lighting with ceiling medallion, and another large window overlooking the front yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to the dining room is the endearing kitchen highlighting a darling wall treatment, abundant fresh white cabinetry and counter space, refreshing lighted ceiling fan, refrigerator, gas range, dishwasher, and disposal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being a ranch home, both bedrooms are on the main level and feature hardwood floors, while one also offers a lighted ceiling fan and the second also highlights a door leading outside and a charming corner built-in hutch. The full bath offers tilework and a shower over tub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs, the full basement is where you will find the laundry area, utility sink, and space for storage or to finish for extra living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, spend time on the patio overlooking the grassy and fenced backyard. What a beautiful spot to enjoy an evening barbecue with family and friends. Additional features include an attached garage with opener and double driveway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG2” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-super-cute-and-move-in-ready-ranch-home.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 06:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-super-cute-and-move-in-ready-ranch-home.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-super-cute-and-move-in-ready-ranch-home.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED and OPEN HOUSE! Beautiful 4 Bedroom Home with Room for Everyone!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xtfgaNUsmJk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3695-n-153rd-street-basehor-ks-66207&quot;&gt;3695 N. 153rd Street, Basehor, KS  66207&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beautiful-4-bedroom-home-with-room-for-everyone&quot;&gt;Beautiful 4 Bedroom Home with Room for Everyone!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This beautiful home was &lt;strong&gt;JUST LISTED&lt;/strong&gt; and we will be hosting the first &lt;strong&gt;OPEN HOUSE&lt;/strong&gt; on &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, May 8th from 12 noon - 4pm!&lt;/strong&gt; We look forward to seeing you and showing you your next home…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://153rd.ihousenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;3695 N. 153rd Street&lt;/a&gt; in the High Point Downs community of Basehor, a spacious four bedroom, three full bath home on a quarter acre lot offering 2,150 square feet of immaculate living space. Some of the many features of this home include a 3-car garage, wood floors, granite counters, stainless steel appliances, vaulted ceilings, master with jetted tub and walk-in closet, family and living rooms, raised deck, and a fenced yard with double gates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://153rd.ihousenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;153rd.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG23” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you approach the home, be greeted by a grassy front yard inviting you to the covered front porch with stacked stone columns and accents. Enter into the open and airy foyer and you will fall in love with the soothing colors and the light and bright living spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The living room features a cathedral ceiling with refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and the focal point of the room is the handsome stacked stone gas fireplace with wood mantel and TV niche above, framed by two large windows&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.The living room opens to the stunning, fully-equipped eat-in kitchen highlighting beautiful wood flooring, pantry, rich and abundant cabinetry, gleaming granite counters with apron sink, full mosaic tile backsplash, and recessed lighting. Stainless steel appliances include the French door refrigerator, smooth surface range, built-in microwave, and dishwasher. The dining area features modern farmhouse style lighting and a door leading to the raised deck. The easy flow of these spaces makes entertaining a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this level you will also find three of the bedrooms, including the enchanting master suite showcasing a multi-tired recessed ceiling with lighted fan, and a gorgeous private full bath featuring a sensational double granite vanity, relaxing spa tub, separate walk-in shower, private water closet, and walk-in closet. There are two secondary bedrooms, the second full bath with a shower over tub, and the laundry room on this level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs is a large family room offering loads of space for entertaining and just hanging out. Also on this level are the fourth bedroom and the third full bath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, you will love to spend time with family and friends on the raised deck overlooking the large, grassy and fenced yard. The level and fenced yard is perfect for kids and pets alike! You will also appreciate the double gates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-and-open-house-beautiful-4-bedroom-home-with-room-for-everyone.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 18:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-and-open-house-beautiful-4-bedroom-home-with-room-for-everyone.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-and-open-house-beautiful-4-bedroom-home-with-room-for-everyone.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ LIKE NEW Beauty Located Close to Ft Leavenworth &amp; Legends Shopping!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vtPOle__rnw?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4409 Ironwood Drive, Leavenworth, KS  66048&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LIKE NEW Beauty Located Close to Ft Leavenworth &amp;amp; Legends Shopping!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://ironwood.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4409 Ironwood Drive&lt;/a&gt;, a beautiful LIKE NEW home on a cul-de-sac, built in 2015 and conveniently located close to Ft. Leavenworth and Legends shopping. Nice open floorplan with 3 bedrooms, 3.5 baths, over 2,000 square feet of finished living space, stainless steel appliances, granite counters, hardwoods, finished basement with full bath, and fenced backyard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://ironwood.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;ironwood.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG25” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be welcomed by a grassy front yard leading to the delightful covered front porch. Step inside and notice the beautiful hardwood flooring as well as the inviting colors that are found through out the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To your left is the dining room featuring the beautiful hardwood floors, chandelier lighting and large windows overlooking the front yard allowing natural light to fill the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hardwoods continue to the eat-in kitchen and great room. The great room highlights a refreshing lighted ceiling fan and more windows providing lovely light and views of the yard. The beautiful fully-equipped kitchen highlights abundant cabinetry, gleaming granite counters, full tile backsplash and stainless steel appliances, including the side-by-side refrigerator with dispensers, smooth surface range, built-in microwave, dishwasher and disposal. Also on the main level are a half bath for the convenience of your guests and a darling hall tree with coat hangers, cubbies, and bench seating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascend the stairs to the bedroom level where you will find all three bedrooms. The master suite features a recessed tray ceiling with refreshing lighted ceiling fan, huge fabulous walk-in closet with built-in shelving, and stunning full bath showcasing an expansive double vanity, gorgeous tiled walk-in shower, tile flooring, separate water closet, and access to the laundry room. Also on this level are two secondary bedrooms, the second full bath, plus the conveniently located bedroom level laundry room with included washer and dryer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs is the finished family room, which is another great spot to gather with family and friends, and the third full bath. There is also an unfinished area great for additional storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, relax on the patio overlooking the grassy, fenced backyard. What a beautiful spot to unwind after a long day. Additional features include an attached 2-car garage and central heating and air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start creating your memories in this beautiful home today! For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;**Photos were taken of the home prior to it being occupied by current tenants.**&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-like-new-beauty-located-close-to-ft-leavenworth-legends-shopping.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 17:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-like-new-beauty-located-close-to-ft-leavenworth-legends-shopping.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-like-new-beauty-located-close-to-ft-leavenworth-legends-shopping.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED! Picture Perfect, Move-in Ready, Cul-de-Sac Home!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/G5DQqU0h--4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;13221-custer-ave-bonner-springs-ks-66012&quot;&gt;13221 Custer Ave, Bonner Springs KS  66012&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;picture-perfect-move-in-ready-cul-de-sac-home&quot;&gt;Picture Perfect, Move-in Ready, Cul-de-Sac Home!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://custer.sdgandassociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;13221 Custer Avenue&lt;/a&gt; in the Deerfield Village community of Bonner Springs. This picture perfect home, located on a beautiful cul-de-sac, offers three bedrooms, two full baths and 1,546 square feet of MOVE-IN READY living space! This home has been freshly painted, inside and out in the last 18 months, and features newer stainless steel appliances, spacious bedrooms, newer privacy fencing, walk-out lower level with rec room, lofted shed, and so much more. You will also appreciate the great location providing easy access to the highway and Village West shopping area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://custer.sdgandassociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Custer.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the amazing details, extensive photo gallery, virtual tour, and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG24” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be welcomed by a grassy front yard with mature ornamental tree inviting you home. The living room features beautiful flooring, a soaring vaulted ceiling with refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and a large window overlooking the front yard allowing natural light to illuminate the room. The focal point of the room is the gorgeous fireplace with natural stone surround and decorative wood mantel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adjacent to the living room is the flawless fully-equipped eat-in kitchen offering the beautiful flooring, abundant cabinetry and counter space, full stone backsplash, and newer stainless steel appliances, including the French door refrigerator with dispensers, smooth surface range, built-in microwave, dishwasher and disposal. The cheery eat-in area features chandelier lighting and a sliding door leading to the raised deck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All three bedrooms are on this main level. The master suite highlights a deep recessed ceiling with refreshing lighted ceiling fan, walk-in closet, and a full private bath with walk-in shower. The two secondary bedrooms each have lighted ceilings fans, and the second full bath features a shower over tub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs, the full finished walk-out lower level is home to a large rec room, another great spot to hang out with friends and family, and also provides access to the backyard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, you will enjoy the multiple spaces for entertaining. Both the raised deck and the covered patio area below allow you to take in the serene views of the large yard with newer 6’ privacy fencing. You will have peace of mind knowing the kids and pets can play safely in their own space, and you will love the included lofted shed, great for storage. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional features include an attached 2-car garage with openers, and central heating and air. This home is the perfect backdrop to start creating lasting memories with those you cherish most!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG24” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-picture-perfect-move-in-ready-cul-de-sac-home.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 14:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-picture-perfect-move-in-ready-cul-de-sac-home.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-picture-perfect-move-in-ready-cul-de-sac-home.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
