<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kansas City Real Estate</title>
    <description>Our mission at SDG and Associates is to be your best resource for Kansas City real estate advice. Whether you are a buyer, seller, or investor, our team of professionals can answer any questions you might have about real estate. If you are looking to buy or sell a home, you can get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from the Shannon Doser Group, your professional Kansas City Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 14:52:49 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 14:52:49 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>NEW LISTING ~ Amazing Layout for Everyday Living and Gathering Friends &amp; Family!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/sxqbZk4AAh0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;17263-w-157th-street-olathe-ks-66062&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://157th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;17263 W. 157th Street, Olathe, KS  66062&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;amazing-layout-for-everyday-living-and-gathering-friends--family&quot;&gt;Amazing Layout for Everyday Living and Gathering Friends &amp;amp; Family!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come FAST … won’t LAST! This front-to-back split has great living space! Stir up some chili in the LARGE KITCHEN with granite counters, an island with bar seating, plenty of storage, and a large adjoining dining area. What an ideal layout for both daily living and entertaining, and, since the kitchen and dining overlook the vaulted living room with fireplace, what a perfect design for gathering friends and family to watch your favorite team when the TV below is tuned to FOOTBALL! Send the kids to the lower level REC ROOM with full bath and door opening to the fenced yard with patio and stairs leading up to a 10x22 DECK just off the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://157th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;157th.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG7” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cute laundry is conveniently located on the bedroom level, just steps from the MASTER SUITE with walk-in closet, tray ceiling, and beautiful bath with dual vanity and shower. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furnace is 1-year new, and A/C is only 5 years old. You’ll also love the 15x22 unfinished basement area accessible from inside the home to store all your extra stuff … solid built-in shelving is ready for your plastic bins. Need plenty of parking space, a work area with built-ins, and a place for that 2nd refrigerator?? MEET the huge OVERSIZED GARAGE! PLUS, avoid the car shuffle in the mornings with the 3-car wide driveway with extra side parking pad!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG7” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/new-listing-amazing-layout-for-everyday-living-and-gathering-friends-family.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/new-listing-amazing-layout-for-everyday-living-and-gathering-friends-family.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/new-listing-amazing-layout-for-everyday-living-and-gathering-friends-family.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ Spacious 5BR Rock Creek Ridge Home with Incredible Floorplan!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oZtwr8Hy_7k?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;879-clearview-drive-lansing-ks-66043&quot;&gt;879 Clearview Drive, Lansing, KS  66043&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;spacious-5br-rock-creek-ridge-home-with-incredible-floorplan&quot;&gt;Spacious 5BR Rock Creek Ridge Home with Incredible Floorplan!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://Clearview.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;879 Clearview Drive&lt;/a&gt; in the Rock Creek Ridge community of Lansing. This spacious home offers 5 bedrooms, 4.5 baths and boasts almost 3,000 square feet of wonderfully laid out living space. Some of the many features to fall in love with include gorgeous hardwood floors, all second level bedrooms with en-suite baths, a fabulous floorplan perfect for everyday living as well as entertaining, and the exterior was freshly painted one year ago. You will also love the location of this home – less than 5 minutes to all Lansing schools, including the new state-of-the-art high school, close proximity to shopping, the Legends, and the Speedway, and Ft. Leavenworth is only a 20 minute drive from this beautiful area. Rock Creek Ridge is also the only community in Lansing with a community pool for summer fun, and there is also a play area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://Clearview.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Clearview.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG3” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you approach the home, notice the amazing landscaping along with the stone and shutter accents inviting you to the covered front porch. Step inside the tiled foyer and be welcomed by a neutral color palette and gorgeous hardwood floors found throughout much of the home. To the left, through 15-lite French doors, is a home office, and to the right of the foyer is the formal dining room featuring crown moulding, chandelier lighting, and a large window overlooking the front yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wood floors continue to the great room offering a cozy gas fireplace with decorative mantel, perfect for the crisp fall evenings, a refreshing lighted ceiling fan, and a large window with views of the backyard allowing natural light to fill the room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The great room is open to the stunning kitchen showcasing rich and abundant cabinetry with under cabinet lighting, gleaming granite counters with stainless steel sink, full tile backsplash, walk-in pantry, and a granite island with eating bar illuminated by whimsical pendant lighting. Stainless steel appliances include the smooth surface range with double ovens, built-in microwave, dishwasher, and disposal. Also on the main level is a powder room for the convenience of your guests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascend the stairs to the bedroom level. The huge master suite highlights a recessed tray ceiling, sitting area, and gorgeous private bath featuring tile flooring, relaxing soaking tub with tile surround, separate walk-in tiled shower with dual shower heads, and double vanity. The second bedroom includes the hardwood flooring and an attached bath with a shower over tub. The large third bedroom highlights a sitting area with built-ins and en-suite access to the Jack-and-Jill bath with double vanity and a shower over tub, shared with the fourth bedroom. You will also appreciate the conveniently located laundry room on the bedroom level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Downstairs is the finished daylight lower level with family rec room, fifth bedroom, fourth full bath with shower, and walk-out to the covered patio and back yard making entertaining a breeze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, entertaining continues on the raised deck with pergola and retractable awning. Stairs lead to the covered patio and grassy yard below with extensive landscaping, the quaint terraced vale, walkway, and firepit – the perfect spot for evening s’mores! Additional features include an attached 3-car garage with openers and keyless entry, central heating and air, humidifier, and sprinkler system with auto timer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG3” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-spacious-5br-rock-creek-ridge-home-with-incredible-floorplan.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-spacious-5br-rock-creek-ridge-home-with-incredible-floorplan.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-spacious-5br-rock-creek-ridge-home-with-incredible-floorplan.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ Beautifully Maintained Corner End-Unit Townhome!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hyBbWZbr3z8?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;10728-w-116th-street-overland-park-ks-66210&quot;&gt;10728 W. 116th Street, Overland Park, KS  66210&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beautifully-maintained-corner-end-unit-townhome&quot;&gt;Beautifully Maintained Corner End-Unit Townhome!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://116th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;10728 W. 116th Street&lt;/a&gt; in the Indian Creek Park Estates of Overland Park. This beautifully maintained, end unit townhome offers three bedrooms, two full plus one half bath, 1,769 square feet of lovely living space, and a great location within the award winning Blue Valley School District. You will also appreciate being close to College Boulevard and highway access. You will love the NEW pergola, freshly painted kitchen and dining room, heated floors in the master bath, and maintenance-provided living, including lawn mowing, snow removal and trash removal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://116th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;116th.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG28” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you approach the home, be greeted by wonderful landscaping, including mature foliage, a grassy front yard, and a mature shade tree welcoming you to the delightful covered front porch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the foyer, continue to the great room and notice the fresh neutral colors, wood trim elements, gorgeous wood floors, lighted ceiling fan, and patio doors opening to the backyard. The focal point of the room is the gas fireplace, perfect for cozy fall evenings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open to the great room is the formal dining room highlighting the beautiful flooring, a vaulted ceiling, drum chandelier lighting, sophisticated wainscoting, eating bar, and a large window overlooking the back yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dining room and great room are both open to the delightful fully equipped kitchen showcasing abundant white cabinetry, gleaming granite counters with undermount sink, full tile backsplash, pantry, and a second breakfast bar looking into the great room. Appliances include the refrigerator with ice maker, gas range, 2-year-new built-in microwave, dishwasher and disposal. Also on the main level are the laundry room and a powder room for the convenience of your guests, featuring a stunning mosaic tile wall accent and gorgeous vessel sink.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascend the stairs illuminated by a skylight to the bedroom level. At the top of the stairs is a peaceful loft area with views to the foyer below. The breathtaking master is your own private retreat showcasing a deep recessed ceiling with lighted ceiling fan, wonderful windows, and spa-like private bath highlighting heated tile flooring, a granite vanity, and a tiled walk-in shower. There are two additional bedrooms and the second full bath with a shower over tub on this level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, you will love to entertain family and friends on the low-profile deck with new pergola overlooking the grassy, privacy fenced yard with shed. Additional features include a full basement, an attached 2-car garage with keyless entry and automatic opener, central heating and air, security system, intercom, and the community amenities, including lawn maintenance, snow removal and trash pick up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG28” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-beautifully-maintained-corner-end-unit-townhome.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-beautifully-maintained-corner-end-unit-townhome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-beautifully-maintained-corner-end-unit-townhome.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NEW LISTING ALERT!  Beautiful EASY LIVING Lenexa Townhome!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6oW-BcfoQyQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;12205-w-79th-terrace-lenexa-ks-66215&quot;&gt;12205 W. 79th Terrace, Lenexa, KS  66215&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beautiful-easy-living-lenexa-townhome&quot;&gt;Beautiful EASY LIVING Lenexa Townhome!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://79th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;12205 W. 79th Terrace&lt;/a&gt;, an EASY LIVING TOWNHOME that’s been pre-inspected and is ready for you to move right in. Fabulous finished basement with full bath can accommodate entertaining or overnight guests with their own sense of privacy. Main floor is open with a fully equipped kitchen, living room/dining room combo, a beautiful fireplace, and atrium door opening to a low profile deck that’s been recently stained and fenced back yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://79th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;79th.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG8” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Retreat upstairs for more privacy – tray ceiling in the master bedroom, along with built-ins, large closet and master bath with soaking tub and shower. There is also a cedar closet in the additional flex space that can be used as a second bedroom, home office or sitting room.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The water heater is less than one year old, the HVAC has been serviced and cleaned, and the roof is in good condition and covered by the HOA for repairs and replacement. Community amenities include a pool, tennis courts, play area, club house and trails. All appliances stay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG8” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/new-listing-alert-beautiful-easy-living-lenexa-townhome.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/new-listing-alert-beautiful-easy-living-lenexa-townhome.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/new-listing-alert-beautiful-easy-living-lenexa-townhome.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ Custom Designed and Built with INCREDIBLE Floor Plan!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/jrM3m9fViZM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;524-edgewood-trail-lees-summit-mo-64081&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://EdgewoodTrail.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;524 Edgewood Trail, Lee’s Summit, MO  64081&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;custom-designed-and-built-with-incredible-floor-plan&quot;&gt;Custom Designed and Built with INCREDIBLE Floor Plan!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to 524 NW Edgewood Trail! This wonderfully MAINTAINED HOME is sited on an approximate half acre wooded lot and has an incredible floor plan for easy living and entertaining, along with a backyard view NOT TO BE BEAT! Custom designed and built, special features and various heights of ceilings, including soaring vaulted ceilings, along with a walk-out basement, all make this home feel even larger than the 3500+ s/f of finished living space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://EdgewoodTrail.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;EdgewoodTrail.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG7” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The LARGE KITCHEN with tasteful granite and all new (2 years old) appliances looks over the vaulted dining area to see a wall of windows with a VIEW over the deck into the beautiful treed backyard. Off the foyer is the flexible FORMAL DINING room with sophisticated wainscoting that also makes for a great office. The stunning GREAT ROOM showcases a soaring cathedral ceiling, cozy gas fireplace, and numerous stacked windows providing lovely natural light to this generously sized space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1st floor MASTER also has a private deck of its own, a very nicely configured walk-in closet, and a large private bath with barrel ceiling, double vanity, and separate tub and shower. Every additional bedroom is generously sized with large closets (2 of them are walk-in closets) and built-ins or vaulted ceilings depending on the room. The second full bath includes a double vanity and separate water closet with shower over tub. Much of the first floor and parts of the 2nd floor were recently painted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The walk-out lower level was finished with a large rec room and a third full bath with shower, still leaving plenty of storage with shelving AND a 14x21 workshop!! 50-year ROOF is only one year old, and the sewer line was completely replace in 2019. All mechanicals have been well maintained, and the home has been consistently monitored by a pest control company. Exterior of home was painted six years ago, and the deck was re-stained within the last year. YOU WON’T WANT TO MISS THIS ONE!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To come see this wonderful home for yourself, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG7” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-custom-designed-and-built-with-incredible-floor-plan.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-custom-designed-and-built-with-incredible-floor-plan.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-custom-designed-and-built-with-incredible-floor-plan.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        <category>Kansas City</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>NEW ON THE MARKET ~ Spectacular Custom Churchill Condo with Panoramic Views</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hnQgf-cbSko?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;803-w-48th-street-804-kansas-city-mo-64112&quot;&gt;803 W. 48th Street, #804, Kansas City MO  64112&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;spectacular-custom-churchill-condo-with-panoramic-views&quot;&gt;Spectacular Custom Churchill Condo with Panoramic Views&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://48th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;803 W 48th Street Unit 804&lt;/a&gt;, a spectacular upscale custom Winston Churchill condo with panoramic views of The Plaza and Brush Creek.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://48th.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;48th.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG6” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Churchill Condos is a modern 12-story building located in the heart of The Plaza, Kansas City’s upscale residential neighborhood and shopping district. Steps away from the Winston Churchill are 14 blocks of beautiful streetscapes boasting over 120 boutiques, local shops, and national retailers. Nearly 30 unique restaurants, cafes, and bars offer an incredible variety of dining options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Churchill amenities include a community penthouse, 24/7 fitness center, clubhouse terrace, secured garage parking, lush landscaping, pet-friendly living, secured entry, and additional storage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This PREMIUM unit was originally two units remodeled into one large unit boasting warm and comfortable finishes, beautiful ebony hardwood floors throughout the kitchen, living room and dining areas, BRAND NEW carpet, master suite with huge walk-in closet and roomy master bath, kitchen with stainless steel appliances, custom cabinetry, wine fridge, granite counters, walk-in pantry, and curved eating bar, an office area, en-suite laundry, two newer HVAC units with zoned heating and cooling, and the majority of window coverings are automated for easy opening and closing. As an added bonus, a frosted glass wall was added to create a media room that is perfect for watching the BIG GAME, like the Super Bowl or World Series! There is abundant storage in the unit and additional storage within the building, and two parking spaces in the secured garage areas are included with the purchase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t get any easier to enjoy living on the Plaza than in the Winston Churchill, and this gorgeous premium unit with its 8th floor views to the south and east is the topper!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To come see this wonderful home for yourself, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG6” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/new-on-the-market-spectacular-custom-churchill-condo-with-panoramic-views.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/new-on-the-market-spectacular-custom-churchill-condo-with-panoramic-views.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/new-on-the-market-spectacular-custom-churchill-condo-with-panoramic-views.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        <category>Kansas City</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED TODAY! 4322 Lloyd Street, Kansas City, KS</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hs0OUV-svlY?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4322-lloyd-st-kansas-city-ks-66103&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://4322Lloyd.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4322 Lloyd St, Kansas City, KS  66103&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;beautifully-renovated-sited-on-a-double-lot-and-great-location&quot;&gt;Beautifully Renovated, Sited on a Double Lot and Great Location! &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BEAUTIFULLY RENOVATED Circa 1905 Craftsman Bungalow sited on a DOUBLE LOT in a GREAT AREA – walk to KU Med, be close to Plaza and Westport, and enjoy quick access to highways and restaurants! This offering includes two lots: the primary home site on Lloyd Street and the vacant fenced lot connected in back on Pearl Street, offering lots of possibilities! This updated gem highlights fresh paint inside and out, new carpet, Google Fiber, charming hardwood floors, classic wood mouldings and trim throughout, exposed brick elements, formal dining room, fully equipped kitchen with breakfast nook, bonus sunroom/office, abundant storage around every corner, detached garage, and raised garden beds currently planted with both veggies and flowers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://4322lloyd.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4322Lloyd.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG2” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be welcomed home by the rocking chair front porch extending the width of the home. What a lovely spot to enjoy a lemonade or hot cocoa with a friend. Enter into the foyer with hardwood floors and notice the handsome Craftsman style wide wood trim and detailing on the stairway, window frames, and baseboards. To your left is the living room with new carpet and a refreshing lighted ceiling fan. Continue to the formal dining room showcasing a delightful bay window with window seat. Abundant windows throughout these spaces provide lots of natural light. Also notice the exposed brick accents in the dining room melding historic building materials with the beautiful renovations.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dining room opens to the fully equipped kitchen with newer refrigerator, gas range with newer vent hood, dishwasher, microwave and disposal. Additional features include abundant cabinetry and counter space, lighted ceiling fan, brick accent wall, and large tile flooring. Enjoy casual meals in the breakfast nook with window overlooking the back yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also located on the main level is a newer powder room for your guests, the laundry room, and a sunroom with wall of windows, which can also be used as an office, study or playroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ascend the handsome staircase to the bedroom level where you will find three bedrooms with new carpet, lots of closets and storage spaces, and ceiling fans, along with a GORGEOUS updated bathroom oozing with charm! Enjoy a soothing bath in the soaking tub or a relaxing shower surrounded by sophisticated tile work.  Hardwood floors and exposed brick accents complete the mood of this quaint bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, there is so much room to relax, entertain or play in the fenced backyard with the extra lot. Whether you dream of expansive gardens, a play area for days, a backyard retreat or building a second home, this extra lot offers so many possibilities. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additional features of this delightful Craftsman Bungalow include the detached garage, long driveway for off street parking, central heating and cooling, storm doors and windows, new electrical panel, upgraded 3-prong grounded outlets, and window coverings. The main sewer line has been cleaned, and plumbing inspected with recommended repairs completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Come start making your lasting memories in this beautiful home filled with the charming details of yesteryear and the modern conveniences of today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG2” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-4322-lloyd-street-kansas-city-ks.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-4322-lloyd-street-kansas-city-ks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-today-4322-lloyd-street-kansas-city-ks.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Home for Sale</category>
        
        <category>Kansas City</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ DARLING Remodeled Ranch Gem on an Oversized Lot!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vyrV9c5DdmQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5343-dearborn-st-mission-ks-66202&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://Dearborn.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;5343 Dearborn St, Mission, KS  66202&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;darling-remodeled-ranch-gem-on-an-oversized-lot&quot;&gt;DARLING Remodeled Ranch Gem on an Oversized Lot!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This DARLING home sits on an oversized lot with plenty of outdoor living space that includes a NEW COMPOSITE DECK, a large patio overlooking the fenced in garden, and a playset that stays. The remodel of this 3 bedroom, 3 1/2 bath home extends beyond the work that was done 1-2 years ago that included a NEW ROOF, NEW kitchen with granite and stainless steel appliances, new carpeting, wood floors, and new 1 and 1/2 bathrooms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://Dearborn.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Dearborn.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG4” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last year, another full bath with DOUBLE VANITY and free standing tub with shower was added, a new grinder pump was installed, downspouts and sump pump discharge were buried, and the French drain was replaced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A 19’ x 65’ double-wide driveway with new gravel provides excellent off-street parking. ALL APPLIANCES STAY, including the washer and dryer. HVAC was recently serviced and the A/C is just 3 years old. There are two outbuildings for plenty of storage for bikes, tools and lawn equipment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The walk-up basement is modestly finished with painted walls, ceiling and flooring. Sunlight infuses the space to enjoy as a kid’s playroom, an exercise room, an office or even another non-conforming bedroom. ONE MORE large storage room is still available in the basement for all your boxes, holiday decorations, luggage, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The laundry has a full size washer and dryer, storage for supplies, and pretty flooring to make the drudgery of laundry a pleasant one! The fireplace in living room is decorative ONLY. A water line was added to the left of the refrigerator with a turn knob to fill your KUERIG. :) There is also an outlet in the drawer of the double vanity to plug in your blow dryer! Yay!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG4” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-darling-remodeled-ranch-gem-on-an-oversized-lot.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-darling-remodeled-ranch-gem-on-an-oversized-lot.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-darling-remodeled-ranch-gem-on-an-oversized-lot.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>LISTING ALERT ~ Well-Maintained Condo Near Westport, The Plaza and KU Med!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ADIUupfd29o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4213-clark-ave-1-kansas-city-mo-64111&quot;&gt;4213 Clark Ave #1, Kansas City, MO  64111&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med&quot;&gt;Well-Maintained Condo Near Westport, The Plaza and KU Med!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome home to &lt;a href=&quot;http://4213clark.sdgandassociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4213 Clark Avenue Unit #1&lt;/a&gt;, a well-maintained and super functional two bedroom, one full bath condo near Westport, The Plaza and KU Med. Enjoy easy access to downtown and convenient walking distance to entertainment and shopping. Whether it’s your first home or an investment property - it’s TURN KEY and ready for YOU! With BRAND NEW carpet throughout, this condo is MOVE IN READY!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://4213clark.SDGandAssociates.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;4213Clark.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG34” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter the home and notice the easy flow between the light and bright living spaces. The living room offers crown moulding and a beautiful wood sliding glass door leading to your private patio. The living room is open to the cheery fully equipped kitchen highlighting large ceramic tile flooring, an abundance of cabinetry and counter space, full tile backsplash with mosaic accents, and an island with bar seating illuminated by pendant lighting. Stainless steel appliances include the refrigerator, smooth surface range, built-in microwave, dishwasher and disposal. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both bedrooms feature refreshing lighted ceiling fans and generous sized closets, while the full bath offers a granite vanity and a shower over tub with lovely tile surround. There is also a stackable washer and dryer that stays with the home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will enjoy being steps away from the private pool and will appreciate the gated parking spot right next to the unit. The community also includes building maintenance, lawn maintenance, and trash pick up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG34” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/listing-alert-well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/listing-alert-well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/listing-alert-well-maintained-condo-near-westport-the-plaza-and-ku-med.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>JUST LISTED ~ Country Living in the City! Beautiful 7 Bedroom on 3.5 Acres!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/J9ocQYB-2dI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;6630-oak-grove-rd-kansas-city-ks-66106&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://oakgrove.ihousenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;6630 Oak Grove Rd&lt;/a&gt;, Kansas City, KS 66106&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;country-living-in-the-city-beautiful-7-bedroom-on-35-acres&quot;&gt;Country Living in the City! Beautiful 7 Bedroom on 3.5 Acres!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Country living in the city! Truly beautiful and one of a kind. Located towards the end of a charming tree-lined country road on over 3.5 acres for privacy. This delightful home is so spacious, boasting 7 bedrooms, 4.1 baths, over 4,000 well-laid-out square feet, a 5-year new roof, and a brand new main floor A/C unit. Set back off the road, a delightful rocking chair porch welcomes you home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://oakgrove.ihousenet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;OakGrove.SDGandAssociates.com&lt;/a&gt; to see all the details, images, virtual tour and current pricing.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG9” to 79564.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enter to the foyer and to your left is the living room and the office, and to your right is the formal dining room. Continue to the family room with a gas log fireplace flanked by built-ins, and beautiful wood doors opening to the back porch, the perfect spot for a morning coffee, refreshing lemonade or evening cocktail. The family room opens to the light &amp;amp; bright kitchen with cook’s island, breakfast area with bay window and pastoral views, and abundant counter and cabinet space. There are also a powder room for your guests and laundry room on this level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upstairs are 5 bedrooms and 3 full baths. The spacious master suite highlights a door opening to the upper veranda, and a private bath with double vanity, large walk-in tiled shower, quaint claw foot tub and walk-in closet with closet system. Several secondary bedrooms include en-suite access to the Jack-and-Jill baths with convenient separate vanities, as well as lighted ceiling fans. One of the bedrooms features a vaulted ceiling and is even spacious enough to use as an upper level family room! Downstairs is the finished walk-out lower level with spacious family rec room, two additional bedrooms with large windows, and 4th full bath.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside, relax, entertain or simply enjoy the expansive country views of this gorgeous acreage. With lots of shade trees for privacy, as well as open lush lawn areas, you have the best of both worlds. There is also plenty of parking with the attached garage and additional off-street/pad parking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What an absolutely charming home to begin making your lasting memories!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information or showing options, call us directly at (913) 906-5489 OR to receive info and pictures to your mobile phone, text “SDG9” to 79564.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=%20http://localhost:4000/just-listed-country-living-in-the-city-beautiful-7-bedroom-on-3-5-acres.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 19:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/just-listed-country-living-in-the-city-beautiful-7-bedroom-on-3-5-acres.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/just-listed-country-living-in-the-city-beautiful-7-bedroom-on-3-5-acres.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
